export const treesData = {
    definition : "A tree is a non-linear data structure that consists of nodes connected by edges. The connections between nodes form a hierarchical structure, where each node has one or more child nodes. Trees are used to represent hierarchical relationships, such as the organization of a company, the file system, or a genetic tree.",
    typesOfTrees: ["Binary Trees: Binary trees are trees with each node having at most two child nodes. They are commonly used in algorithms like binary search.","N-ary Trees: N-ary trees allow for more than two child nodes per node. They are often used to represent organizational hierarchies or data structures like XML documents.","Heaps: Heaps are specialized tree-based data structures that satisfy the heap property. They are used in algorithms like heapsort and priority queues.","Tries: Tries are trees used for efficient text search and data compression. They are based on the prefix property of words."],
    operations: ["Insertion: Adding a new node to the tree.","Deletion: Removing a node from the tree.","Traversal: Traversing the tree to visit all nodes in a specific order, such as pre-order, in-order, or post-order.","Searching: Finding a particular node in the tree."],
    questions: [
        {
            title: "Invert Binary Tree",
            id:"226",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/invert-binary-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0226/?h=226",
        },
        {
            title: "Maximum Depth of Binary Tree",
            id:"104",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/maximum-depth-of-binary-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0104/?h=104",
        },
        {
            title: "Diameter of Binary Tree",
            id:"543",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/diameter-of-binary-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0543/?h=543",
        },
        {
            title: "Balanced Binary Tree",
            id:"110",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/balanced-binary-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0110/?h=110",
        },
        {
            title: "Same Tree",
            id:"100",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/same-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0100/?h=100",
        },
        {
            title: "Subtree of Another Tree",
            id:"572",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/subtree-of-another-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0572/?h=572",
        },
        {
            title: "Lowest Common Ancestor of a Binary Search Tree",
            id:"235",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/lowest-common-ancestor-of-a-binary-search-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0235/?h=235",
        },
        {
            title: "Binary Tree Level Order Traversal",
            id:"102",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-level-order-traversal/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0102/?h=102",
        },
        {
            title: "Binary Tree Right Side View",
            id:"199",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-right-side-view/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0199/?h=199",
        },
        {
            title: "Count Good Nodes in Binary Tree",
            id:"1448",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-good-nodes-in-binary-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1448/?h=1448",
        },
        {
            title: "Validate Binary Search Tree",
            id:"98",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/validate-binary-search-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0098/?h=98",
        },
        {
            title: "Kth Smallest Element in a BST",
            id:"230",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/kth-smallest-element-in-a-bst/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0230/?h=230",
        },
        {
            title: "Construct Binary Tree from Preorder and Inorder Traversal",
            id:"105",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/construct-binary-tree-from-preorder-and-inorder-traversal/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0105/?h=105",
        },
        {
            title: "Binary Tree Maximum Path Sum",
            id:"124",
            difficulty: "Hard",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/binary-tree-maximum-path-sum/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0124/?h=124",
        },
        {
            title: "Serialize and Deserialize Binary Tree",
            id:"297",
            difficulty: "Hard",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/serialize-and-deserialize-binary-tree/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0297/?h=0297",
        },
    ]
}